[{"product_id":1,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Harry","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1612.92,"dues":5,"product_sku":"HPT001001","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp","discount":18.93,"stock":5},{"product_id":2,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Hermione","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1775.98,"dues":4,"product_sku":"HPT001002","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp","discount":15.67,"stock":5},{"product_id":3,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luna","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1621.2,"dues":7,"product_sku":"HPT001003","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp","discount":2.21,"stock":1},{"product_id":4,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Snape Patronus","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1601.92,"dues":5,"product_sku":"HPT001004","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp","discount":7.1,"stock":3},{"product_id":5,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Charmander","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1825.14,"dues":3,"product_sku":"PKM001001","img_front":"/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp","discount":3.86,"stock":3},{"product_id":6,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Dragonite","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1787.61,"dues":5,"product_sku":"PKM001002","img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp","discount":0.58,"stock":4},{"product_id":7,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pidgeotto","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1615.23,"dues":7,"product_sku":"PKM001003","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp","discount":7.57,"stock":1},{"product_id":8,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Pikachu","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1605.59,"dues":0,"product_sku":"PKM001004","img_front":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp","discount":9.15,"stock":4},{"product_id":9,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Vulpix","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":2033.34,"dues":12,"product_sku":"PKM001005","img_front":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp","discount":8.71,"stock":2},{"product_id":10,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Baby Yoda","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1688.61,"dues":5,"product_sku":"STW001001","img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp","discount":14.44,"stock":2},{"product_id":11,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Bobba Feth","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1847.48,"dues":3,"product_sku":"STW001002","img_front":"/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp","discount":11.2,"stock":2},{"product_id":12,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luke","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1648.19,"dues":1,"product_sku":"STW001003","img_front":"/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp","discount":2.15,"stock":0},{"product_id":13,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Trooper","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1959.91,"dues":5,"product_sku":"STW001004","img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp","discount":15.79,"stock":1}]